So I have a question for y'all with locks with 4C hair.
Can you tell me what is your preferred, thank you Coach Turner for, can you tell me what
is your preferred pomade or ointment, ointment is not really the word, but like, what do
you like to use for your twist up?
So, those of you with the 4C, style factor, I use all products from Mango and Lime, okay
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, let me make a list, hold on, oh God, let me make a
list.
Okay, we have raw aloe, then some, hold on, hold on, oh God, so all you say you like, raw
aloe is the one you like, I've seen multiple people say that.
Kaleidoscope, the Brat Line, so, okay, African Shea Butter, raw aloe, I don't find that Taliyah
Waleed would hold, because it doesn't really hold mine, eh?
You hear my accent.
Okay, mango and lime, style factor, and someone else has said, shea butter.
Okay, when I say this, don't act up, don't act up when I say this, for a man.
Okay, so we're using the kaleidoscope on nephews, okay, so, Jamaican black caster butter, still
lock and gel, okay, okay, that's what I'm thinking, it's royal lead, like, I feel like
it's going to create residue and build up.
The question is, what, um, what to use for, for palm roll, for 4C hair locks.
All right, I see people saying shea butter is water and light castor oil from Brand Creole
Essence.
The buildup is the biggest issue.
Like, my hair doesn't really get buildup, because it's soft, you know?
But 4C will hold it.
Mousse from Design Essentials.
Okay.
I knew y'all would have some answers, honey.
If you need to get rid of frizz, you need to learn how to crochet, or you need to get
someone to crochet it, because the crochet is literally taking the frizz and using it,
putting it back into the lock, but not putting it in the lock.
You're basically reinforcing the strength of the lock with the frizz.
Y'all are the best in the world.
Ooh, now, come on, now, you know, you know this thing is, is moving fast.
You got it, you got it, you got it.
All right.
Thank you, Emily.
Yes, I'm coming back to radio as of next week.
So this person's locks are thick.
So it's like, they need to be interlocked, then crocheted at the interlock, but then also,
you know, you got to put a little, you know what I mean, to just keep it clean.
So I'm just, but their texture is different than mine.
You can listen to me.
You got to download the KBLM.
I know interlocking is a tricky game because interlocking to me is like counterintuitive
to locking because you got to split the lock.
So I'm like, what are we doing?
What are you doing?
But that is always set up.
So I, that is always done.
That's how theirs is done.
So I'm just keeping with the rhythm, y'all.
I'm just, I'm just keeping with the rhythm.
I'm just keeping with the rhythm.
Now we learn how to do locks.
Okay.
You know what?
Not me remembering how to do locks.
Because at this point, y'all, when you find yourself just like able to do something mad
easy, know that you're remembering.
It's not like, oh, I'm just naturally good at this.
You're remembering.
This is something that you've done either in another dimension or in another body.
When I say that you're not splitting the lock, when I say you're splitting the lock, I just
mean like you're splitting the, you're, you're, the roots are not locked.
Yes.
I am aware of this.
However, it just feels like counterintuitive to the thickening.
But I guess that's why you do that and then you crochet over it.
That, I mean, there, that does make sense to a certain extent.
Where do I get this information from?
Quantum physics and also in ancient indigenous knowledge.
Any other, anything else?
You see, this is shit that has been known throughout ancient knowledge.
Like Indian been talking about this, uh, Africa been talking about this, Asia been talking
about, well, India's in Asia, but different parts of Asia have been talking about this
for centuries.
This is a part of Ayurvedic knowledge.
It's a part of, um, ancient Egyptian knowledge.
It's a part of ancient Chinese knowledge.
Right?
And so one of the things that I'm trying to break y'all out of, I'm trying to get y'all
to understand that what you have right now is not knowledge.
We have lies.
Anything that you have been taught, anything that, that we've been taught that has us thinking
that this, this is it, those are lies.
That was never how people existed or thought ever.
And then quantum physics came out and was like, hold up, hold up.
Oh, Kung Fu Lenny.
I don't, um, I don't keep people like that in my circle.
So then quantum physics gets, gets in the mix and they like, Hey, guess what?
These ancient people have been right the whole time.
And now we're co-signing it with science.
Anything that has you believing you're not powerful, know that that's a lie that has been
treated, that has literally been told to you for that exact purpose.
So think about it.
If you're able to consciously change your reality, if you're able to envision beyond the
limitations of this fucked up world, then you become capable of changing this world.
And this world is ruled by folks who have no interest in changing it because it gives them
power.
They believe in the occult.
They do rituals.
They've been doing all type of nonsense for thousands of years.
It's talked about.
It's even, I know y'all love that Bible.
Ooh, I know y'all love that Bible.
And it is talked about in the Bible.
Okay.
So other body, well, we're in 3D.
There's 4D dimensions and 5D.
And then your soul inhabits bodies.
And then that body dies and that energy is still living.
So when your ancestors are speaking to you, those are souls that are still in existence
that either have reincarnated or not, but their energy and their essence is still out
here.
And this is, this has been understood.
I want, I don't want to say believed.
It's been understood by indigenous people forever.
I use Talia Waleed, but I, it is no shade to her.
I just don't think it works the best with me.
It's just that I've been, I just been too lazy to get, to try something better.
So, you know, that's where I'm, I'm taking my work now.
Like for instance, tonight we have the Radical Rhythms Experience, Radical Rhythms Experience.
You can watch it on YouTube at seven, it's at eight, it's at 8 p.m. Eastern.
So the link is in my bio.
I'm, I'm really trying to do something different y'all.
I'm trying to combine my gift of comedy and music with energy, not energy work and leveling
up our vibration work.
Like that's what I'm trying to do.
And it's a process.
That's what I'm trying to do.
And the reason why I'm trying to do it is because everything we have to do to undo all
of the corruption and all of the evil that's happening in this world requires us to be
solid.
We were broken.
That's why we haven't been able to fucking change the shit.
And now we have the planets actually in alignment in a way that is like supporting us.
So this is an auspicious time for us to get our shit together.
This is the time.
And, and I want you to know, like some people, they're not going to get it.
And that's, you know, that's, that's not for you to convince them.
Lean into your practice.
So, um, if you watch the film, everything, everywhere, all at once, like they do a good
job of putting into context, like these, these, these concepts.
I think the easiest way to explain it is this.
So you have like an X axis, you have a Y axis, and then you have a Z.
Okay.
So think of like, so think of it like, like this.
So this right here is going forward, right?
But it's really going sideways.
So it looks like it's going forward because that's how we live in 3D.
We live linear, but it's really going sideways.
So imagine copying that.
This is infinity, right?
So in this third dimension, we're existing in this, in many different forms, because we
are all made of electrons and electrons basically shift depending on the choices that you make.
This is quantum physics.
Like this is not some made up shit.
Science has come to be like, damn, them all has had it.
Them all has had it.
They had it.
So there's you in this, and then there's you in this, and you in this, like you're living
in multiple dimensions.
So that nigga that you fucking with right now, that ain't shit, you can change that.
Do something different.
Change your timeline.
You jump to a different timeline.
Right?
Then this is the Y axis.
This is your body.
So the same way this is going, this is also going, you're in multiple bodies.
So you're in multiple bodies in multiple timelines.
Because this around here, this is the 4D.
This is consciousness.
And inhabits all of this.
So here's, here's you in multiple timelines.
But remember, this goes up.
So you got this in multiple timelines.
And then you got different bodies in multiple timelines.
It's wild.
And you can jump.
You can change.
You can change it.
Like scientifically, it's like, yes.
And these motherfuckers built a machine called CERN that understands this and was fucking with the timelines.
When you're watching shows like Stranger Things, yes, you can jump timelines.
When you're watching shows like Stranger Things and you think this is fantasy, no, it's not.
They telling you what they doing.
They fucking with the timelines.
So if they fucking with your timelines, you should fuck with it back.
Make different decisions.
You see how we keep being in a time loop?
You see how we keep coming back to the same shit?
People are like, oh my God, they're taking our voting rights.
Yes, they've done it twice before.
We're back.
Because like everything, and I know y'all love that Bible.
And what do they say in that Bible?
They're going to teach you the same lesson over and over and over again.
Over and over and over again.
Until you learn it.
That is literally the human experience.
And we're not learning the lesson.
Make different decisions.
Right?
And I want you to know the decision don't have to be no big fucking thing.
The decision doesn't have to be a big, big, big, big thing.
Sometimes take a different route home.
If you always answer the phone for this person that's always draining you, don't this time.
If you're always eating that thing that you love but you know is not good for you, don't this time.
If you're always denying yourself that thing that you really want to do but you tell yourself like, oh, I'm too old for that or, oh, I don't have time for that.
Make time.
Change your timeline.
Where is God in all of this?
Baby, we are, we are in God's image.
We are God.
That's what I'm trying to get folks to understand.
Imagine if we treated each other the way that with the respect and regard that we respect and regard God with.
God is in all of us.
It's very easy to believe in something outside of yourself because it alleviates you of responsibility.
It's very easy.
It's very easy to be like, oh, I believe in Jesus.
He's over there.
It's very easy.
It's a whole other thing when you hold yourself to that.
When you're like, yo, appreciate you, JC.
Oh, my love, you are.
You are of God.
You are not God, but you are of God.
All of us are.
We are here for some reason that requires all of us to understand this in order to reclaim this planet that is very fucking special.
So the sooner that we do that, because they are constantly convincing us that we are toxic, that we are terrible, that we are ignorant.
And when I say they, I mean those who are here that have chosen to disregard that in order to believe in dark magic and in the occult.
These are the ones who are doing the rituals, who are drinking the blood, who are eating the children, who are in the Epstein files.
This is not some made up shit.
They want you to believe it's fake because then you won't fucking stop it.
And you will begin to stop it if you start with you.
What can you articulate what you think makes making a new choice easier said than done for folks?
So, and I'll be talking about this tonight on Radical Rhythms Experience.
No, I love the questions.
I love the questions to you, Genia.
You have great questions.
Keep them coming.
So, rhythm, so energy is rhythmic.
Energy moves in a circle, right?
So that's why you see storms move in a circle.
That's why you see the earth.
Whether you think the earth is flat or not, it's a circle, okay?
So, circles come back around.
What does rhythm do?
It's continuous, right?
It's continuous.
It comes back around.
Your heart is rhythm.
Your mother said you're a Jezebel?
Fuck your mother.
That's some bullshit.
Don't listen to her.
Why would she even say that to you?
Even if she felt that way, there's a much more loving and useful way to share that information with you.
I don't like that.
These mothers be wilding out here and I don't like it.
All right.
So, your heart is rhythm, okay?
But your heart is not the only rhythm in your body.
Your body is on a rhythm on a regular basis to function because your body is an engine, right?
It's a system.
So, just like with any other engine, if the rhythm gets fucked up, the usefulness of it gets fucked up.
That's why when we eat certain foods that throw off our body's ability to process, that's why when we do certain things that fuck up our body's ability to process, it throws off our rhythm.
It throws off our energy.
It throws off our health, etc.
So, rhythm is how we exist.
We exist in rhythm.
So, when you ask, oh my God, Ryan, really?
So, when you ask, why are things easier said than done?
It's because it's hard for people to change the rhythm they've locked into.
And so often, we lock in to a bullshit fucked up ass rhythm.
We got multiple rhythms going just like we got multiple dimensions going.
And then you find out that there's been literally knowledge about this forever that has been manipulated.
And so, when you hear hip-hop, which is rhythm, and then they use it to tell you messages that make you hate yourself, that make you undermine yourself, know that they are using energy to disrupt your energy.
So, we have to bring it back.
I mean, I ain't gonna lie to you, T.
That's what I think.
And whenever I see white people with rhythm, I be like, oh, you in a new body.
But your soul came from somewhere else.
You in a new body.
You in this white body, but your soul came from somewhere else.
So, you know, when people talk about like, oh, Amanda was so difficult in Hollywood, et cetera.
That's why they fired you from such and such and such and such.
I'm like, yeah.
Because their rhythm is chaos.
It is radical to reclaim our rhythm.
And Crash 180, your rhythm is your own rhythm.
It doesn't have to be chaotic.
We are literally living in disordinate sound and rhythm.
Like, I'm autistic and my autism is innately connected to music.
I'm intuitive and my intuition is innately connected to time.
And those two things are innately connected to energy.
And if you notice, in all indigenous peoples, I'm talking from Ireland to Siberia to the Gosa in South Africa,
all of them have a drum at the center of their living.
Not just at the center of, you know, rituals.
No, it's at the center of their living.
Because the drum is the rhythm.
And the rhythm is life.
To feel the rhythm of life.
It is to feel the rhythm of life.
It's a powerful beat.
Feel the rhythm of your tongue and the rhythm of your feet.
So, when we say march to your own drum, that's what that is.
You are your own drum.
But they trying to make you march to some other fucking nonsense.
So that they can control you.
No.
We got to get back to our own rhythms.
And we got to learn how to love each other's different rhythms.
And also, we got to learn how to respect like,
oh, baby, your rhythm doesn't vibe with my rhythm.
All good.
Just don't fuck up my rhythm.
And we good.
You over there.
That's it.
You know, I saw, I had something on my stories today, this morning.
And it was like, it said, I'll never,
it was like a video I saw that said,
I'll never forget when I was having a really hard time
and you made it more difficult for me.
And I tagged five people in that.
Because I'll never forget when they fucked up my rhythm.
I'll never forget when my rhythm was being fucked with.
And they was like, yeah.
Nope.
I'll never forget that.
But what I did learn was that I can control my rhythm.
And I'm using the word rhythm because I think it's easier for folks to grasp.
Because I think the word energy be throwing people off.
You know, because it's gotten kind of like misappropriated and woo woo.
So let's bring it back to the rhythm.
The biggest thing you have to understand is that
nothing about this existence is simple.
Nothing about this is simple.
They've tricked you into thinking it's basic life and death
so that they can just use you and dispose of you.
Absolutely not.
And when people leave you in this life,
they are still here with you.
Because energy lives on.
I'm so proud of you, flower child.
I'm so proud of you.
You can't let people fuck with your rhythm, bro.
I love my mother.
I can't be around my mother.
She don't protect my rhythm.
Only key people around you
who protect your rhythm.
You understand me?
And that doesn't always have to be acrimonious.
It can literally just be,
you know what?
Our rhythm don't align right now.
So I'm gonna let you go and rock on.
T, I think sometimes we can't feel certain energies
because we're not at a point to feel them yet.
This takes work.
We've been a part of a psychological operation
for 60 years minimum.
We have been, we have been disconnected.
We're numb.
So we gotta bring it back.
That's literally what I'm doing
with Radical Rhythm Experience.
So I hope y'all will join me tonight
at 7.50 Eastern on live.
And you can come to join me in Harlem
at Comedy in Harlem on 147th and St. Nick
at 17 bucks.
Come through.
I'm trying to, I'm trying to bring,
I'm trying to merge these artistic gifts I have
with this energy knowledge that I'm remembering
to bring those of us who don't have access to this
into this.
So T, one of the things I would suggest to do
if you can, is try to spend more time in nature.
Nature opens you up.
Do the best you can, sweet Leo.
When you start consciously saying,
I'm not gonna let these people fuck up my rhythm.
It really changes you, your life.
It really changes your life.
Well, T, you come from,
so heat is the sun.
You're a black woman.
So you literally get stronger in the sun
unless you're like being worked beyond your fair means.
But sun strengthens melanin.
You're talking about bugs.
Bugs are insects.
Bugs are souls.
We're all a part of this.
And then you're talking about dirt.
Well, what do you think you,
what do you think gives you nutrients to eat?
Dirt.
Sun and dirt.
You know what that sounds like to me?
Healing.
But like Nat said right here,
if that ain't your jazz, go buy water.
Nature exists in multiple forms.
You know, nature exists in multiple forms.
So it's really,
I did not watch Disclosure Day.
Do I need to?
We gonna get there.
Abby, we gonna get there.
So I hope to see y'all tonight.
My link is in the bio.
Radical Rhythms Experience.
Thank you, Jam Good Living.
Jam on it.
Jamming on the one.
You don't sound crazy.
You just sound curious.
And to be quite honest,
that's where you gotta start.
You gotta start at curiosity.
You know, we have been really, really fucked with
and convinced that curiosity is a nuisance, right?
Like how many times you hear,
oh, they ask too many questions.
Get the hell out of here, B.
If the questions are for the elevation,
then there's never too many questions.
So tonight's topic at the Radical Rhythms Experience
is freedom.
Freedom.
So I will be talking about freedom
and we will be talking about freedom together.
Next month, I think the topic is gonna be authenticity.
So everything that I've said here,
you know, you don't gotta ever take what I'm saying as like bar none.
I hope that when I say things,
if you already know about it,
you like, yeah, yeah, nigga.
And then if you don't know about it,
I hope you're like, hmm, let me get curious.
What's she talking about with this quantum physics stuff?
What's she talking about with this third dimension,
4D dimension, fifth dimension stuff?
What's she talking about about this,
you know, holographic existence stuff?
Thank you, Nat.
I appreciate you.
That's a big deal.
Well, Ryan, authenticity vibrates higher than love
because authenticity is self-love.
It's the full embracing of your soul.
It's literally the full embracing.
It's your purest form.
Living in your full authentic self,
that's pure.
And pure, as you know, is undistilled.
It's concentrate.
So that's, you know, my book,
my children's book that's coming out in October
is called A Children's Book of Being Authentic.
We gotta get our kids to be authentic.
We gotta let them know that they can be who they are
and that we're gonna love them
and we're gonna inspire them
and we're gonna support them.
We're gonna guide them, right?
We're gonna inform them.
However, ultimately,
we're gonna let them remind us how to be authentic
and we're gonna teach them
that authenticity in yourself at the core
is how you begin to live in honesty and truth.
And I'm telling you,
if you can convince,
if you can finally admit
to living in honesty and truth all the time,
like sometimes we have these moments
where we've got to tell a white lie,
catch yourself.
Catch yourself.
Don't tell that white lie.
That's why whenever people tell me
that I should just go along
with a politician who's lying,
I'm like,
what are we talking about?
What are we talking about?
The longer we support lying as a way of life,
the longer we will live in this lie
and it's killing us.
It's killing us.
Honesty and truth gets you,
honesty and truth doesn't get you in trouble.
Honesty and truth forces you out of spaces
that do not respect honesty and truth.
And it's challenging you to find another path
and to find other spaces that do.
Receive the challenge.
That's why my album is called Truth Translator
because we are all capable of being truth translators
and we need to start holding each other to that level.
Okay?
So I'm about to go
and I will see you all this evening
and I hope that you have
a great rest of your Wednesday.
A great rest of your hump day.